Guide to the Charles Hamm Recordings, 1857-1999 HAMM.2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Recordings on LP, 1
  - Popular, 1871-1999; IX.
    - Chicago VI, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0066)
      This album includes Critics choice -- Just you 'n' me -- Darlin' dear -- Jenny -- What's this world comin' to -- Something in this city changes people -- Hollywood -- In terms of two -- Rediscovery -- Feelin' stronger every day.
    - Chicago VII, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0067)
      This album includes Prelude to Aire -- Aire -- Devil's sweet -- Haliau from New York -- Hanky panky -- Life saver -- Happy man -- I've been searching so long -- Mongonucleosis -- Song of the evergreens -- Byblos -- Wishing you were here -- Call on me -- Women don't want to love me -- Skinny boy.
    - Chicago VIII, 1974-1975 (Record HAMM POP 0068)
      This album includes Anyway you want -- Brand new love affair-Part I -- Brand new love affair-Part II -- Never been in love before -- Hideaway -- Till we meet again -- Harry Truman -- Oh, thank you great spirit -- Long time no see -- Ain't it blue? -- Old days.
    - The Dave Clark Five: Satisfied with You, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0069)
      This album includes Satisfied with you -- Go on -- Do you still love me? -- I meant you -- Look before you leap -- Please tell me why -- You never listen -- I still need you -- It'll only hurt for a little while -- Good lovin'.
    - 20 Years of Rock n Roll, 1953, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0070)
      This album includes Crying in the chapel (Orioles) -- Sh-boom (Life could be a dream) (Crew Cuts) -- Rock around the clock (Bill Haley) -- Blue suede shoes (Carl Perkins) -- I walk the line (Johnny Cash) -- I'm walkin' (Fats Domino) -- Whole lotta shakin' goin' on (Jerry Lee Lewis) -- Rebel rouser (Duane Eddy) -- All I have to do is dream (Everly Brothers) -- Put your head on my shoulder (Paul Anka) -- Why (Frankie Avalon) -- Sweet nothings (Brenda Lee) -- Runaround Sue (Dion) -- Soldier boy (Shirelles) -- Peppermint twist (Joey Dee) -- Louie, Louie (Kingsmen) -- Leader of the pack (Shangri-Las) -- Wooly Bully (Sam the Sham & The Pharoahs) -- You've lost that lovin' feeling (Righteous Brothers) -- Hang on Sloopy (McCoys) -- Do you believe in magic (Lovin' Spoonful) -- Good lovin' (Young Rascals) -- Brown-eyed girl (Van Morrison) -- Dock of the bay (Otis Redding) -- Crimson & clover (Tommy James) -- Oh happy day (Edwin Hawkins) -- Candles in the rain (Melanie) -- Super fly (Curtis Mayfield) -- So you're leaving (Al Green) -- Nice to be with you (Gallery). SUBJECT(S)
    - The Clash: Black Market Clash, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0071)
      This album includes Capital radio one -- The prisoner -- Pressure drop -- Cheat -- City of the dead -- Time is tight -- Bankrobber/Robber dub -- Armagideon time -- Justice tonight/Kick it over.
    - The Clash: Sandinista!, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0072)
      This album includes The magnificent seven -- Hitsville U.K. -- Junco partner -- Ivan meets G.I. Joe -- The leader -- Something about England -- Rebel waltz -- Look here -- The crooked beat -- Somebody got murdered -- One more time -- One more dub -- Lightning strikes (not once but twice) -- Up in heaven (not only here) -- Corner soul -- Let's go crazy -- If music could talk -- The sound of the sinners -- Police on my back -- Midnight log -- The equaliser -- The call up -- Washington bullets -- Broadway -- Lose this skin -- Charlie don't surf --Mensforth Hill -- Junkie slip -- Kingston advice -- The street parade --Version City -- Living in fame -- Silicone on sapphire -- Version pardner -- Career opportunities -- Shepherds delight.
    - Eddie Cochran: 12 of his Biggest Hits, 1900 (Record HAMM POP 0073)
      This album includes C'mon everybody - Thre steps to heaven - Cut across shortly - Have I told you lately that I love you - Hallelujah, I love her so - Sittin' in the balcony - Summertime blues - Lovin' time - Somethin' else - Tell me why - Teenage heaven - Drive in show.
    - Songs of Leonard Cohen, 1960-1969 (Record HAMM POP 0074)
      This album includes Suzanne.--Master song.--Winter lady.--The stranger song.--Sisters of mercy.--So long, Marianne.--Hey, that's no way to say goodbye.--Stories of the street.--Teachers.--One of us cannot be wrong.
    - Judy Collins: Who Knows Where the time Goes, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0075)
      This album includes Hello, hooray (4:07) -- Story of Isaac (3:30) -- My father (4:55) -- Someday soon (3:43) -- Who knows where the time goes (4:20) -- Poor immigrant (4:04) -- First boy I loved (6:29) -- Bird on the wire (4:37) -- Pretty Polly (5:47).
    - Judy Collins: Judith, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0076)
      This album includes The moon is a harsh mistress -- Angel, spread your wings --Houses -- The loving of the game -- Song for Duke -- Send in the clowns -- Salt of the earth -- Brother, can you spare a dime -- City of New Orleans -- I'll be seeing you -- Pirate ships -- Born to the breed.
    - Ry Cooder: Bop Till You Drop, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0077)
      This album includes Little sister -- Go home, girl -- The very thing that makes you rich -- I think it's going to work out fine -- Down in Hollywood -- Look at Granny run run -- Trouble, you can't fool me -- Don't you mess up a good thing -- I can't win.
    - Ry Cooder: Show Time, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0078)
      This album includes School is out -- Alimony -- Jesus on the mainline -- The dark end of the street -- Viva Sequin -- Do re mi -- Volver, volver -- How can a poor man stand such times and live -- Smack dab in the middle.
    - Alice Cooper: Billion Dollar Babies, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0079)
      This album includes Hello hooray / Rolf Kempf (4:14) -- Raped and freezin' (3:15) -- Elected (4:05) -- Billion dollar babies (3:39) -- Unfinished sweet (6:17) -- No more Mr. Nice Guy (3:05) -- Generation landslide (4:31) -- Sick things (4:18) -- Mary Ann (2:19) -- I love the dead (5:08).
    - Alice Cooper: Love it to Death, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0080)
      This album includes Caught in a dream (M. Bruce -3:04) -- I'm Eighteen (M. Bruce, [et al] -3:00) -- Long way to go (M. Bruce -3:01) -- Black Juju (D. Dunaway -9:09) -- Is it my body (A. Cooper, [et al] -2:39) -- Hallowed be my name (N. Smith -2:25) -- Second coming (A. Cooper -3:02) -- Ballad of Dwight Fry (M. Bruce, A. Cooper -6:32) -- Sun arise (Butler, Harris -3:53).
    - Elvis Costello: My Aim is True, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0081)
      This album includes Welcome to the working week -- Miracle man -- No dancing -- Blame it on Cain -- Alison -- Sneaky feelings -- Watching the detectives -- (The angels wanna wear my) red shoes -- Less than zero -- Mystery dance -- Pay it back -- I'm not angry -- Waiting for the end of the world.
    - Country Joe and the Fish: Here We Are Again:, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0082)
      This album includes Here I go again -- Donovan's Reef -- It's so nice to have love -- Baby, you're driving me crazy -- Crystal blues -- For no reason -- I'll survive -- Maria -- My girl -- Doctor of electricity.
    - Creedence Clearwater Revival: Chronicle, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0083)
      This album includes Susie Q. / Hawkins (4:36) -- I put a spell on you / Jay Hawkins (4:30) -- Proud Mary (3:07) -- Bad moon rising (2:18) -- Lodi (3:10) -- Green river (2:32) -- Commotion (2:41) -- Down on the corner (2:39) -- Fortunate son (2:18) -- Travelin' band (2:06) -- Who'll stop the rain (2:27) -- Up around the bend (2:41) -- Run through the jungle (3:05) -- Lookin' out my back door (2:31) -- Long as I can see the light / J.C. Fogerty (3:33) -- I heard it through the grapevine / Whitfield (3:52) -- Have you ever seen the rain? (2:39) -- Hey tonight (2:43) -- Sweet hitch-hiker (2:57 ) -- Somebody never comes / J.C. Fogerty (3:59).
    - Cream: Wheels of Fire, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0084)
      This album includes In the studio: White room -- Sitting on top of the world -- Passing the time -- As you said -- Pressed rat and warthog -- Politician -- Those were the days -- Born under a bad sign -- Deserted cities of the heart -- Live at the Fillmore: Crossroads -- Spoonful -- Traintime -- Toad.
    - Jim Croce: The Faces I've Been, 1972, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0086)
      This album includes This land is your land -- Greenback dollar -- Pig's song -- Gunga Din -- Sun come up -- Big fat woman -- Charlie Green play that slide trombone -- Railroads and riverboats -- Railroad song -- The way we used to -- Maybe tomorrow -- Stone walls -- I remember Mary -- Country girl -- Which way are you goin' -- King's song -- Mississippi lady -- Chain gang medley: Chain gang; He don't love you; Searchin's -- Old man river -- Carmella...South Philly -- Cars and dates, chrome and clubs -- The Chinese -- Trucks and ups -- The army.
    - Crossing Oceans (Record HAMM POP 0087)
      This album includes All in vain - Foxy Lady - Restless waiting - False accusation - The rooster's story - Get up and move - Brown sugar - I wish - Crazy horse - The warden.
    - Cruisin' 1961, 1983 (Record HAMM POP 0088)
      This album includes Blue moon / Marcells -- My true story / Jive Five -- Johnny B. Goode / Chuck Berry -- But I do / Clarence "Frogman" Henry -- Purple people eater / Sheb Wooley -- Tossin' and turnin' / Bobby Lewis -- Runaway / Del Shannon -- Barbara Ann / Regents -- Ya ya / Lee Dorsey -- Hide away / Freddie King.
    - David and David: Boomtown, 1986 (Record HAMM POP 0089)
      This album includes Welcome to the boomtown -- Swallowed by the cracks -- Ain't so easy -- Being alone together -- A rock for the forgotten -- River's gonna rise -- Swimming in the ocean -- All alone in the big city -- Heroes.
    - John Denver: Aerie, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0090)
      This album includes Downhill stuff -- Sweet Melinda -- What's on your mind -- Joseph & Joe -- Life is so good -- Berkeley woman -- Johnny B. Goode -- You're so beautiful -- Southwind -- Garden song -- Songs of....
    - Derek and the Dominos: Layla, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0091)
      This alubm includes I looked away -- Bell bottom blues -- Keep on growing -- Nobody knows you when you're down and out -- I am yours -- Anyday -- Key to the highway -- Tell the truth -- Why does love got to be so sad -- Have you ever loved a woman -- Little wing -- It's too late -- Layla -- Thorn tree in the garden.
    - Surfin' with Bo Diddley, 1963 (Record HAMM POP 0092)
      This album includes What did I say -- White silver sands -- Surfboard cha cha -- Surf, sink, or swim -- Piggy back surfers -- Surfers love call --Twisting waves -- Wishy washy -- Hucklebuck -- Old man river -- Oop's he slipped -- Low tide.
    - Disco Fire, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0093)
      This album includes Dance dance dance -- It's ecstasy when you lay down next to me -- Which way is up -- Devil's gun -- Two hot for love -- Star wars title theme -- I feel love -- Flash light -- Boogie shoes -- Gonna fly now -- You keep me dancing -- I can't stand the rain -- Disco inferno -- Keep it comin' love -- Dazz -- Risky changes -- Dance across the floor -- Don't let me be misunderstood -- Best of my love -- Running away -- Ma Baker -- Chattanooga choo choo -- Let's all chant -- Dance with me.
    - Discopedia Vol. 2, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0094)
      This album includes MacArthur Park -- Boogie, oogie, oogie -- San Francisco/In Hollywood -- Manhattan skyline.
    - Donovan: Barabajagal, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0095)
      This album includes Barabajagal -- Superlungs my supergirl -- Where is she -- Happiness runs -- I love my shirt -- The love song -- To Susan on the west coast waiting -- Atlantis -- Trudi -- Pamela Jo.
    - Donovan: For Little Ones, 1967 (Record HAMM POP 0096)
      This album includes Song of the naturalist's wife -- The enchanted gypsy -- Voyage into the golden screen -- Isle of Islay -- The mandolin man and his secret --Lay of the last tinker -- The tinker and the crab -- Widow with a shawl (a portrait) -- The lullaby of spring -- The magpie -- Starfish-on-the-toast --Epistle to Derroll.
    - Donovan's Greatest Hits, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0097)
      This album includes Epistle to dippy (3:10) -- Sunshine superman (4:30) -- There is a mountain (2:38) -- Jennifer juniper (2:40) -- Wear your love like heaven (2:24) -- Season of the witch (4:46) -- Mellow yellow (3:42) -- Colours (4:20) -- Hurdy gurdy man (3:18) -- Catch the wind (5:04) -- Lalena (2:52).
    - Donovan in Concert, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0098)
      This album includes Isle of Islay -- Young girl blues -- There is a mountain -- Poor cow -- Celeste -- The fat angel -- Guinevere -- Widow with shawl (A portrait) --Preachin'love -- The lullaby of spring -- Writer in the sun -- Pebble and the man -- Rules and regulations -- Mellow yellow.
    - Doors, 1967 (Record HAMM POP 0099)
      This album includes Break on through -- Soul kitchen -- The crystal ship -- Twentieth Century Fox -- Alabama song -- Light my fire -- Back door man -- I looked at you -- End of the night -- Take it as it comes -- The end.
    - Carol Douglas: Burnin', 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0100)
      This album includes Fell in love for the first time today -- Burnin' -- Let's get down to doin' it tonight -- Night fever -- Let you come into my life -- So you win again -- All my love.
    - Bob Dylan/The Band: Before The Flood, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0101)
      This album includes Most likely you go your way (and I'll go mine)--Lay, lady, lay.--Rainy day women.--Knockin' on heaven's door.--It ain't me, babe.--Ballad of a thin man.--Up on Cripple Creek.--I shall be released.--Endless highway.--The night they drove old Dixie down.--Stage fright.--Don't think twice, it's all right.--Just like a woman.--It's alright, ma (I'm only bleeding)--The shape I'm in.--When you awake.--The weight.--All along the watchtower.--Highway 61 revisited.--Like a rolling stone.--Blowin' in the wind.
    - Bob Dylan, 1962 (Record HAMM POP 0102)
      This album includes She's no good -- Talkin' New York -- In my time of dyin' -- Man of constant sorrow -- Fixin' to die -- Pretty Peggy-O -- Highway 51 -- Gospel plow -- Baby, let me follow you down -- House of the risin' sun -- Freight train blues -- Song to Woody -- See that my grave is kept clean.
    - Bob Dylan: Bringing it all Back Home, 1965 (Record HAMM POP 0103)
      This album includes Subterranean homesick blues -- She belongs to me -- Maggie's farm -- Love minus zero; No limit -- Outlaw blues -- On the road again -- Bob Dylan's 115th dream -- Mr. Tambourine man -- Gates of Eden -- It's alright, ma, (I'm only bleeding) -- It's all over now, baby blue.
    - Bob Dylan: Highway 61 Revisited, 1965 (Record HAMM POP 0104)
      This album includes Like a rolling stone -- Tombstone blues -- It takes a lot to laugh, it takes a train to cry -- From a Buick 6 -- Ballad of a thin man -- Queen Jane approximately -- Highway 61 revisited -- Just like Tom Thumb's blues --Desolation row.
    - Bob Dylan: John Wesley Harding, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0105)
      This album includes John Wesley Harding -- As I went out one morning -- I dreamed I saw St. Augustine -- All along the watchtower -- The ballad of Frankie Lee and Judas Priest -- Drifter's escape -- Dear landlord -- I am a lonesome hobo -- I pity the poor immigrant -- The wicked messenger -- Down along the cove -- I'll be your baby tonight.
    - Bob Dylan: Nashville Skyline, 1969-1970 (Record HAMM POP 0106)
      This album includes Girl from the north country (with Johnny Cash) -- Nashville skyline rag -- To be alone with you -- I threw it all away -- Peggy day -- Lay lady lay -- One more night -- Tell me that it isn't true -- Country pie -- Tonight I'll be staying here with you.
    - Bob Dylan: The Freewheelin', 1963 (Record HAMM POP 0107)
      This album includes Blowin' in the wind -- Girl from the North country -- Masters of war -- Down the highway -- Oxford town -- Bob Dylan's blues -- A hard rain's a-gonna fall -- Don't think twice -- It's all right -- Bob Dylan's dream --Talking World War III blues -- Corrina, Corrina -- Honey, just allow me one more chance -- I shall be free.
    - Bob Dylan: The Times They Are A-Changing, 1964 (Record HAMM POP 0108)
      This album includes The times they are a-changin' -- Ballad of Hollis Brown -- With God on our side -- One too many mornings -- North country blues -- Only a pawn in their game -- Boots of Spanish leather -- When the ship comes in -- The loneseome death of Hattie Carroll -- Restless farewell.
    - Eagles: Hotel California, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0109)
      This album includes Hotel California (6:30) - New kid in town (5:4) -- Life in the fast lane (4:46) -- Wasted time (4:55) -- Wasted time (reprise) (1:22) -- Victim of love (4:11) -- Pretty maids all in a row (4:5) -- Try and love again (5:10) -- The last resort (7:25).
    - Eagles: One of these Nights, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0110)
      This album includes One of these nights -- Too many hands -- Hollywood waltz --Journey of the sorcerer -- Lyin' eyes -- Take it to the limit -- Visions --After the thrill is gone -- I wish you peace.
    - Earth, Wind & Fire: All n All, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0111)
      This album includes Serpentine Fire (3:51) - Fantasy (4:38) - In the marketplace (Interlude--3:55) - Jupiter - Love's holiday (5:43) - Brazilian Rhyme (Interlude) - I'll write a song for you (5:23) - Magic mind (3:39) - Runnin' (6:45) - Brazilian Rhyme (Interlude) - Be ever wonderful (5:08).
    - England's Greatest Hitmakers, 1965 (Record HAMM POP 0112)
      This album includes Surprise, surprise (The Rolliing Stones) -- Soon I'll wed my love (Kathy Kirby) -- Little girl (Them) -- Kiss kiss (Tom Jones) -- Sandstorm (The Mike Leander orchestra) -- Woman from Liberia (Unit Four plus Two ) -- Forget her (Bern Elliott) -- Maureen (The Bachelors) -- Nothing's changed (The Zombies) -- Just one look (Lulu and the Luvers) -- Tomboy (The Johnny Howard Band) -- This diamond ring (Billy Fury) -- Baby's in black (Tha Applejacks) -- He's with you (Dave Berry).
    - Eurythmics: Touch, 1983 (Record HAMM POP 0113)
      This album includes Here comes the rain again (4:54) -- Regrets (4:43) --Right by your side (4:05) -- Cool blue (4:48) -- Who's that girl (4:46) -- The first cut (4:44) -- Aqua (4:36) -- No fear, no hate, no pain (no broken hearts) (5:24) -- Paint a rumor (7:30).
    - The Everly Brothers: Pass the Chicken and Listen, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0114)
      This album includes Lay it down -- Husbands and wives -- Woman, don't try to tie me down -- Sweet memories -- Ladies love outlaws -- Not fade away -- Watching it go -- Paradise -- Somebody nobody knows -- Good hearted woman -- A nickel for the fiddler -- Rocky Top.
    - Emerson Lake & Palmer: The Best of, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0115)
      This album includes Hoedown -- Lucky man -- Karn evil 9 (1st impression, part 2) -- Jerusalem -- Peter Gunn --Fanfare for the common man -- Still ... you turn me on -- Tiger in a spotlight -- Trilogy.
    - Emerson Lake & Palmer: Welcome Back, My Friends, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0116)
      This album includes Hoedown - Jerusalem - Tocata - Tarkus (Eruption--Stones of years--Iconoclast--Mass--Manticore--Battlefield) - Tarkus (Conclusion)--Aquatarkus - Take a pebble - Piano improvisations - Take a pebble (conclusion) - Jeremy Bender/The sheriff (medley) - Karn evil 9 (1st Imression) - Karn evil 9 (2nd Impression--3rd Impression).
    - Emerson Lake & Palmer: Works, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0117)
      This album includes Piano concerto no. 1, by K. Emerson, with the London Philharmonic Orchestra.--Lend your love to me tonight.--C'est la vie.--Hallowed be thy name.--Nobody loves you like I do.--Closer to believing.--The enemy god; Dances with the black spirits (excerpts from The Scythian Suite, 2d movement, by S. Prokofieff).--L.A. Nights.--New Orleans.--Two part invention in D minor, by J. Bach, arr. by C. Palmer.--Food for your soul.--Tank.--Fanfare for the common man, by A. Copland.--Pirates.
    - My Life in the Bush of Ghosts, 1981 (Record HAMM POP 0118)
      This album includes America is waiting -- Mea culpa -- Regiment -- Help me somebody -- The jezebel spirit -- Qu'ran -- Moonlight in glory -- The carrier -- A scret life -- Come with us -- Mountain of neeles.
    - The 5th Dimension: Greatest Hits on Earth, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0119)
      This album includes (Last night) I didn't get to sleep at all--Stoned soul picnic--One less bell to answer--Medley: Aquarius/let the sunshine in (The flesh failures)--Wedding bell blues--Save the country--Love's lines, angles and rhymes--Puppet man--Up, Up and away--Never my love--Together let's find love.
    - Roberta Flack: Killing Me Softly, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0120)
      This album includes Killing me softly with his song (4:46) -- Jesse (4:00) -- No tears (in the end) (4:56) -- I'm the girl (4:52) -- River (5:00) -- Conversation love (3:38) -- When you smile (3:42) -- Suzanne (9:45).
    - Fleetwood Mac: Rumours, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0121)
      This album includes Second hand news -- Dreams -- Never going back again -- Don't stop -- Go your own way -- Songbird -- The chain -- You make loving fun -- I don't want to know -- Oh daddy -- Gold dust woman.
    - The Flowerpot Men, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0122)
      This album includes Melting down on motor angel (The Flowerpot Men) - Walk on gilded splinters (Mac Rebennack Skull Music).
    - Dan Fogelberg: Phoeniz, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0123)
      This album includes Tullamore dew (1:15) -- Phoenix (7:05) -- Gypsy wind (4:01) -- The last to know (3:09) -- Face the fire (5:40) -- Wishing on the moon (4:32) --Heart hotels (4:13) -- Longer (3:14) -- Beggar's game (5:00) -- Along the road(4:47).
    - Four Tops Greatest Hits, Vol. 2, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0124)
      This album includes In these changing times -- Still water (love) -- Still water (peace) -- Don't let him take your love from me -- It's all in the game -- I'm in a different world -- If I were a carpenter -- What is a man -- Walk away Renee -- You keep running away -- Yesterday's dreams -- Just seven numbers (can straighten out my life).
    - The Four Seasons: Story, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0125)
      This album includes Sherry -- Big girls don't cry -- Walk like a man -- Stay -- Marlena -- Don't think twice -- Candy girl -- Dawn -- C'mon Marianne -- Opus 17 (Don't worry 'bout me) -- Workin' my way back to you -- Let's hang on -- Ronnie -- Bye bye baby (baby goodbye) -- Rag doll -- Beggin' -- Silence is golden -- I've got you under my skin -- Save it for me -- Big man in town -- Will you still love me (tomorrow) -- And that reminds me -- Electric stories -- Watch the flowers grow -- Tell it to the rain -- Ain't that a shame -- Toy soldier -- Alone.
    - Foreigner, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0126)
      This album includes Feels like the first time -- Cold as ice -- Starrider -- Headknocker -- The damage is done -- Long, long way from home -- Woman oh woman -- At war with the world -- Fool for you anyway -- I need you.
    - Frampton Comes Alive, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0127)
      This album includes Something's happening (5:54) -- Doobie wah (5:28) -- Show me the way (4:42) -- It's a plain shame (4:21) -- All I want to be (is by your side) (3:27) -- Wind of charge (2:47) -- Baby, I love your way (4:43) -- I wanna go to the sun (7:02) -- Penny for your thoughts (1:23) -- (I'll give you) Money (5:39) -- Shine on (3:35) -- Jumping Jack flash (7:45) -- Lines on my face (7:06) -- Do you feel like we do (14:15).
    - Fripp & Eno: Evening Star, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0128)
      This album includes Wind on water (5:35) -- Evening star (7:41) -- Evensong (2:47) -- Wind on wind (3:04) -- An index of metals (27:55).
    - Golden Soul, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 129)